{
  "chapter": 21,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Which among the following stands as limitation(s) for mobile computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Processing capability",
        "Storage capacity",
        "Battery power",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Through which technique, the energy conservation can be done in mobile computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Task offloading",
        "Data offloading",
        "Communication offloading",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following cannot be considered as a limitation of mobile computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource at computing device",
        "Network bandwidth",
        "Mobility of computing device",
        "Power of battery"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The resource-rich computing system used for augmenting resources of mobile computing device is referred as",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Master system",
        "Surrogate system",
        "Secondary system",
        "Server system"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "In mobile-cloud computing, which among the following is used in the resource augmentation process?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Any non-mobile system",
        "Mobile cloud server",
        "Cloud server",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Mobile cloud computing solves which of the following limitation(s) of traditional mobile computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource limitation",
        "Vendor-lock-in",
        "Energy limitation",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "When task offloading from one end device to other end devices is done instead of cloud that is called as",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mobile computing",
        "Fog computing",
        "Internet of Things",
        "Traditional computing"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following is an essential attribute of smart object?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "High-end processing capability",
        "Large storage capability",
        "Fast communication capability",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following contributes most in the emergence of IoT?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cloud computing",
        "Fog computing",
        "Smart object",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Smart objects need to have physical existence. This statement is:",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which IP addressing standard is suitable for uniquely identifying objects in IoT?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["IPv4", "IPv6", "Any IP standard", "None of these"],
      "answer": 2
    }
  ]
}
